Contact

laurenicurn08@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/lauren-davis-a7903012b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Basic Life Support (BLS) CCRN

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Lauren Davis

Nurse Manager Novant Health Forsyth Medical Center MHA/MBA, BSN, RN, CCRN

Winston Salem, North Carolina

Summary

Experienced nurse leader in acute care with a variety of clinical settings including critical care, nephrology, and limb preservation. Diverse professional preparation with a Master of Healthcare Administration/Master of Business Administration from Pfeiffer University in addition to a Bachelor of Science in Nursing from Western Carolina University.

Experience

Novant Health

12 years 1 month

Nurse Manager

November 2015 - Present (4 years 9 months)

Winston Salem, North Carolina

Critical Care RN-Clinical Unit Leader

March 2015 - November 2015 (9 months)

Winston Salem, North Carolina

Critical Care Registered Nurse

July 2008 - March 2015 (6 years 9 months)

Winston Salem, North Carolina

Education

Pfeiffer University

Master of Healthcare Administration/Master of Business Administration, Healthcare Administration (2015 - 2017)

Western Carolina University

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2004 - 2008)